# ChangSeok Oh

Profile: https://shivamidow.github.io E-mail: changseok@gnome.org Mobile: +1 (404) 740-7896

Open-source enthusiast and hacker specializing in web technology and Linux-based systems. A WebKit and GNOME project contributor. More than 8 years of experience at major players in the industry. Looking for opportunities in the Web browser, Web Security & Privacy, Browser Security, Kernel, and Computer Graphics.

Skills

WebKit, Blink/Chromium, GNOME, Linux, C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Objective-C, Java, OpenGL/OpenGL ES, Clutter, Computer Graphics, GTK+, eBPF, BCC, Ethereum, Git, OBS, Clang, LLVM, GStreamer, Tizen, Linux Perf, Bluetooth LE, ReactJS, React Native, Embedded system, Puppeteer

#### Education

08/2017 - 12/2022	Ph.D. student (ABD) in Cybersecurity & Privacy, Georgia Tech, U.S.A.
08/2019 - 12/2022	M.S. in Cybersecurity, Georgia Tech, U.S.A.
08/2017 - 08/2019	M.S. in Computer Science (Concentration: Systems), Georgia Tech, U.S.A.
03/2000 - 06/2008	Dual B.E. in Digital Media and Computer Engineering, Ajou University, South Korea

## Professional Experience

06/2019 - present	Intern at Igalia, S.L. in A Coruña, Spain
	Bring ANGLE backend for WebGL to WebKitGTK
	<ul> <li>Zero copy texture sharing between Mesa and ANGLE via Linux DMA buffer</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Research Text-To-Speach technologies to employ for WebKitGTK</li> </ul>
05/2020 - 08/2020	Intern at Samsung Research America in Mountain View, CA
05/2019 - 08/2019	<ul> <li>Build a web app for health data analysis with ReactJS (frontend) and Node.js (backend)</li> </ul>
	• Built an automated system verifying the UI of a watch app by using the Tizen automation framework
	<ul> <li>Profiled memory usage and revealed possible memory leak of a watch app by using Valgrind</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Implemented file transfer via Bluetooth LE in a React Native watch application</li> </ul>
08/2012 - 03/2016	Software engineer at Collabora Ltd. in Cambridge, UK
	<ul> <li>Developed hardware-based compositing based on Clutter in WebKit</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Resource-efficient web browser based on GNOME Epiphany for Raspberry Pi 2+</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Customized WebKit features and API set for Smart TV Alliance SDK</li> </ul>
07/2008 - 08/2012	Assistant Software engineer at Samsung Electronics in Suwon, South Korea
	• Developed an in-house web layout engine for Smart TVs, Printers in C++
	<ul> <li>Implemented WebGL and Accelerated Compositing in WebKit EFL by using OpenGL ES for Tizen</li> </ul>
07/2007 - 06/2008	Intern at Samsung Software Membership in Suwon, South Korea
	<ul> <li>Developed a 3D racing game using DirectX on Windows (video)</li> </ul>

#### Academic Experience

icadomic Zaportonec	
05/2021 - 08/2021	Research Intern at Tandon School of Engineering, New York University
	Research an online ad privacy issue with Prof. Damon McCoy
08/2019 - 05/2021	Teaching Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech
	• CS 6262: Network Security, Design and Implement the XSS task using node.js and Chrome Extension
	CS 6035: Intro to InfoSec
08/2017 - present	Research Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech
	Study privacy leakage in online ads
	Redesign chromium to block user tracking by web browser fingerprints
	Debloat chrome browser with feature sunsetting on the fly by binary rewriting
	• Developed a defense system against micro DDoS by profiling resources with HPC (Intel PCM, MBM)
	• Implemented an idle profiler that diagnoses off-CPU time in the multi-threaded programs using HPC

### Open Source Projects

open Source Projects		
04/2013 - present	Committer at WebKit (patches)	
	• Implement several web features for WebKitGTK (e.g., Form validation, Gamepad API with libmanette,	
	AVIF support with dav1d, Web Speech with Flite, etc)	
	• Implement OpenGL ES backend for Accelerated Compositing.	
	• Developed memory pressure handler that copes with out-of-memory on top of Linux cgroup.	
	<ul> <li>Enhance WebGL support and Fix layout and rendering issues</li> </ul>	
	• Fix CVE security bugs in WebKit (CVE-2020-10018, CVE-2020-11793)	
10/2013 - present	Member at GNOME Foundation (patches)	
	Translate GNOME Web and its Help document in Korean	
01/2015 - present	Contributor at Chromium/Blink (patches)	
	• Implemented a CSS spec called font-size-adjust	
	Fix layout and rendering issues in Blink	

#### **Publication**

CCS 2020 arXiv:2205.00056	Slimium: Debloating the Chromium Browser with Feature Subsetting (paper) Mitigating Low-volume DoS Attacks with Data-driven Resource Accounting (paper)	
Patents		
US 20110296323 US 20110289110 US 20110093606 US 20110090165	Web page management method and apparatus and storage medium thereof Method of re-searching webpage and apparatus and storage medium therefor Interface method and display device Interface method and display device	
Talks		
12/07/2014 09/29/2014 04/25/2014 10/27/2013	DEVIEW 2014 in Seoul, South Korea (slides, video) Jeju University in Jeju, South Korea (slides)	
Service		
10/2021	Mentoring participants in the Open-source SW Developer Competition in South Korea	

Last updated: 08/21/2022